{
    "subject": "resource/Bishop_Grimes_Junior/Senior_High_School",
    "predicate": "property/country",
    "object": "USA",
    "human_readable": "Bishop Grimes Junior/Senior High School is located in USA.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.982620894908905,
            "question": "Where is Bishop Grimes Junior/Senior High School located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9623180031776428,
            "question": "In what country is Bishop Grimes Junior/Senior High School situated?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9005333781242371,
            "question": "What type of school is Bishop Grimes Junior/Senior High School?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.840167760848999,
            "question": "Is Bishop Grimes Junior/Senior High School a public or private institution?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7947288155555725,
            "question": "Does Bishop Grimes Junior/Senior High School offer both junior and senior levels of education?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7808206677436829,
            "question": "What is the history behind the establishment of Bishop Grimes Junior/Senior High School?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7465636730194092,
            "question": "Are there any notable alumni from Bishop Grimes Junior/Senior High School?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7462928891181946,
            "question": "What is the approximate student population at Bishop Grimes Junior/Senior High School?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.731611967086792,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about the educational programs offered at Bishop Grimes Junior/Senior High School?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5755500793457031,
            "question": "Does Bishop Grimes Junior/Senior High School have any unique extracurricular activities or clubs?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Bishop Grimes Junior/Senior High School is located in USA.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4004_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me more about the educational programs offered at Bishop Grimes Junior/Senior High School?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4004_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the approximate student population at Bishop Grimes Junior/Senior High School?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4004_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any notable alumni from Bishop Grimes Junior/Senior High School?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4004_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4004_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4004_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4004_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4004_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4004_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4004_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4004_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4004_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4004_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4004_57.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n\n\n**Explanation:**\n\nThe document states that Bishop Grimes Junior/Senior High School is \"in East Syracuse, New York\" and Greenheart highlights this school as being located within the USA.   Therefore, the triple is supported by the documents. \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents mention that Bishop Grimes Junior/Senior High School is located in East Syracuse, New York, which confirms its location within the United States."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {'output': 'yes'}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}